Jocselyn Aguilar

Full Stack Engineer with experience in Python, Django, Angular and Docker. I also have knowledge of Java, Spring Boot, React and AWS. I am Proactive and adaptable. I seek to continue growing professionally and contribute my skills to challenging projects.

Costa Rica(Heredia)

(506) 6339-91-35

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jocselyn-a

https://josandre.github.io/ProfessionalPortfolio/

EXPERIENCIA

EEDS, Remote: Front-End Engineer

May 2023 - October 2023

Web application created using Angular 13 together with libraries such as Bootstrap and Angular Material. Direct work with the client to collect requirements and model the application.

4Geeks, Remote: Full Stack Engineer

August 2023 - March 2024

Full stack developer with a strong focus on Python and Angular., focused at integrating and maintaining advanced technologies, such as Stripe for payment processing, Typesense for search functionality, and OpenAl for resume analysis, as well as the management and enhancing client projects, ensuring seamless operation and continuous improvement.

Limbo, Remoto: Apprentice and Volunteer in Full Stack

April 2022-August 2023

As a volunteer and apprentice of the program, I led the development of a web application from the beginning, dedicating time to acquiring skills in the technologies to be used, including GraphQL, React, Typescript and NodeJS. I also had the responsibility of imparting my knowledge to new students in the program, and I also held the role of instructor at Cenfotec University, covering topics such as object-oriented programming and programming fundamentals.

FORMACIÓN

Cenfotec University, San josé: Bachelor of Software Engineering

January 2021 - December 2024

REFERENCES

Andre Solis – Software Engineer – Professor – Limbo Founder rlip@limbodev.com Erick Brenes – Software Engineer – Professor – EEDS Founder erick.brenes.u@gmail.com Allan Porras - Software Engineer – 4Geeks Founder alpocr@4geeks.io

APTITUDES

Autodidact.

Disciplined..

Consistent.

Passionate.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Bloom Web application designed and created to help people suffering from anxiety, integrated with a panic button, so that users could ask for help when needed.

Cenfoteco Kingdoms Desktop game using design patterns in Java, LibGDX was used for the application interface. This game was chosen to be presented at the university's Maker Fest in June 2023.

Waze of thrones Project created in C++, using non-linear data structures, mainly using the Dijkstra graph algorithm..

LANGUAGES

Spanish

English